<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Welcome To Our Team]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Welcome To Our Team]]></description>
        <link>http://surewayfinancial.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 01:25:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://surewayfinancial.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 01:25:16 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[View SFG Video]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Sureway Financial partnered with Symmetry Financial Group</p>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FMV8AUTd6C8U%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DMV8AUTd6C8U&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FMV8AUTd6C8U%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<p>Sureway Financial partnered with Symmetry Financial Group was established with the goal of bringing balance to the professional and personal lives of independent insurance agents and agency builders across the country.</p>,<blockquote>NO COLD CALLING &amp; NO DOOR TO DOOR SALES!</blockquote>,<p><strong>Exclusive Warm Lead Program That Places You In Front of Buyers. Our clients have requested our services after retaining a new mortgage.</strong></p>,<blockquote>If you&apos;re looking for the ability to make a great living while helping people, this could be the opportunity for you!</blockquote>,<a href="https://calendly.com/surewaytolive" data-role="cta">Schedule A Call</a>,<p><strong>Symmetry Financial Group</strong>, Fastest growing insurance organization in USA, headquartered in Asheville, NC. Our agents are located all across America. We have over 50 years of industry experience and offer a variety of financial and insurance solutions leveraging the very best providers in the country. SFG has grown from a few hundred thousand dollars in sales in 2009 to $11 million in 2015.</p>,<p><strong>Work Right Out of Your Home: </strong>We focus on earning both TIME &amp; MONEY, the definition of true wealth. Our agents spend 2-3 days a week meeting with clients. The rest of the work is done from the comfort of your own home.</p>,<blockquote>World Class Incentive Trips &amp; Bonuses: Our agents participate in trips most people dream about. Barcelona, Maui, Cancun, Naples, and Alaska are just some of the destinations our agents will travel to in 2017, all provided by our carriers!</blockquote>,<p><strong>The Leads Department is The Cornerstone of Symmetry Financial Group:</strong> Their purpose is to streamline the sales process by placing agents in front of buyers, thus eliminating the need for prospecting. From the very first phone call until the final sale and application, our CRM Software allows agents to manage their client database.</p>,<a href="https://calendly.com/surewaytolive" data-role="cta">Schedule A Call</a>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2Fvideoseries%3Flist%3DPLTZVUzQQJrcaszNxOnbtnTNnYY-IWjmw3&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DCtC5EN_dNBI&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FCtC5EN_dNBI%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://surewayfinancial.com/view-sfg-video/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09713388-7348-4d9c-ac2d-64a892f5082b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>